{
    "questions": [
        {
            "qid": 1,
            "question": "Dart is an?",
            "options": [
                "Open-source",
                "General purpose",
                "Programming language",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 4
        },
        {
            "qid": 2,
            "question": "Dart is developed by?",
            "options": [
                "Microsoft",
                "Facebook",
                "Google",
                "IBM"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "qid": 3,
            "question": "The _______ function is a predefined method in Dart.",
            "options": [
                "declare()",
                "list()",
                "main()",
                "return()"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "qid": 4,
            "question": "Dart is an Object-Oriented language.",
            "options": [
                "Yes",
                "No"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "qid": 5,
            "question": "Which function is responsible for starting the Dart program?",
            "options": [
                "runApp()",
                "main()",
                "run()",
                "flutter()"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 6,
            "question": "A notable feature of the Dart platform is its support for “hot reload”",
            "options": [
                "False",
                "True"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 7,
            "question": "The Dart language can be compiled",
            "options": [
                "AOT",
                "JIT",
                "Both AOT and JIT",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "qid": 8,
            "question": "Is Dart a case sensitive language?",
            "options": [
                "Yes",
                "No"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "qid": 9,
            "question": "Is Dart static or dynamic language?",
            "options": [
                "Statically typed language",
                "Dynamically typed language",
                "Both A and B",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "qid": 10,
            "question": "Is Dart interpreted or compiled?",
            "options": [
                "Interpreted language",
                "Compiler language",
                "Interpreted Compiler language",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        }
    ]
}